{"classes":["LANGUAGE","GENRE","GPE","TITLE","PERSON","WORK","DATE"],"annotations":[["Give me a movie in hindi directed by Ram Gopal Verma shot in India.",{"entities":[[19,24,"LANGUAGE"],[25,33,"WORK"],[37,52,"PERSON"],[61,66,"GPE"]]}],["Which are all movies shot in USA in 2005.",{"entities":[[29,32,"GPE"],[36,40,"DATE"]]}],["For each year from 2015 to 2019 for each genre, Adventure, and Drama.",{"entities":[[19,23,"DATE"],[27,31,"DATE"],[48,57,"GENRE"],[63,68,"GENRE"]]}],["What's the Chris Nolan film where time goes backwards?",{"entities":[[11,22,"PERSON"]]}],["What's the name of that Netflix film made by Martin Scorsese?",{"entities":[[45,60,"PERSON"]]}],["Give me the name of scifi movie from 2000 to 2020 directed by Ryan Cooler.",{"entities":[[20,25,"GENRE"],[37,41,"DATE"],[45,49,"DATE"],[62,73,"PERSON"]]}],["Name the DC movie that Todd Phillips directed.",{"entities":[[23,36,"PERSON"],[37,45,"WORK"]]}],["She loves watching sci-fi movies because they take her to imaginative, otherworldly places.",{"entities":[[19,25,"GENRE"]]}],["Show me the cast of 'Star Wars' movie.",{"entities":[[20,31,"TITLE"]]}],["Which adventure flick did Leonardo DiCaprio win an Oscar for?",{"entities":[[6,15,"GENRE"],[26,43,"PERSON"]]}],["The club is putting on a production of Romeo and Juliet.",{"entities":[[39,44,"PERSON"],[49,55,"PERSON"]]}],["What was that space movie produced by Stanley Kubrick?",{"entities":[[14,19,"GENRE"],[26,34,"WORK"],[38,53,"PERSON"]]}],["All comedy movies produced by Will Smith in french.",{"entities":[[4,10,"GENRE"],[30,40,"PERSON"],[44,50,"LANGUAGE"]]}],["Which are all marathi series shot in 1996 composed by Shubham Bhagwat.",{"entities":[[14,21,"LANGUAGE"],[37,41,"DATE"],[42,50,"WORK"],[54,69,"PERSON"]]}],["The crime rate in the city has been steadily decreasing over the past few years.",{"entities":[[4,9,"GENRE"]]}],["All japanese movies show in Sweden produced by James Benning released in 1930.",{"entities":[[4,12,"LANGUAGE"],[28,34,"GPE"],[35,43,"WORK"],[47,60,"PERSON"],[73,77,"DATE"]]}],["Give me a name of romantic movie from 2004 directed by Yash Chopra.",{"entities":[[18,26,"GENRE"],[38,42,"DATE"],[43,51,"WORK"],[55,66,"PERSON"]]}],["Give me a name of actress from 'King Authur: Legend of the Sword' movie.",{"entities":[[31,65,"TITLE"]]}],["All movies with title 'Fast and Furious' released after 2005.",{"entities":[[22,40,"TITLE"],[56,60,"DATE"]]}],["What was the first Tarantino film that Christoph Waltz appeared in?",{"entities":[[19,28,"PERSON"],[39,54,"PERSON"]]}],["A documentary with music composed by Alfred Russo.",{"entities":[[2,13,"GENRE"],[25,33,"WORK"],[37,49,"PERSON"]]}],["She loves watching romance movies because they make her feel happy and hopeful.",{"entities":[[19,26,"GENRE"]]}],["Give me a fictional movie in English directed by James Cameron.",{"entities":[[10,19,"GENRE"],[29,36,"LANGUAGE"],[37,45,"WORK"],[49,62,"PERSON"]]}],["Give me an English documentary of the Royal family released in 2022.",{"entities":[[11,18,"LANGUAGE"],[19,30,"GENRE"],[63,67,"DATE"]]}],["Show me all the movies that were released in the United States in the year 2000.",{"entities":[[49,62,"GPE"],[75,79,"DATE"]]}],["List all the movies that Tom Hanks has starred in.",{"entities":[[25,34,"PERSON"]]}],["Give me a name of scifi movie in spanish directed by Mel Gibson.",{"entities":[[18,23,"GENRE"],[33,40,"LANGUAGE"],[41,49,"WORK"],[53,63,"PERSON"]]}],["Give me a drama movie in hindi directed by Sanjal Leela Bhansali shot in India.",{"entities":[[10,15,"GENRE"],[25,30,"LANGUAGE"],[31,39,"WORK"],[43,64,"PERSON"],[73,78,"GPE"]]}],["Find all the movies that were released in the 1980s and are in the comedy genre.",{"entities":[[46,51,"DATE"],[67,73,"GENRE"]]}],["Show me the top rated movies that were released in the UK.",{"entities":[[55,57,"GPE"]]}],["List all the movies that were released in Spain and are in the thriller genre.",{"entities":[[42,51,"GPE"],[63,71,"GENRE"]]}],["Find all the movies that have English and Spanish audio.",{"entities":[[30,37,"LANGUAGE"],[42,49,"LANGUAGE"]]}],["Give me a series directed by Tim burton which is released recently.",{"entities":[[17,25,"WORK"],[29,39,"PERSON"]]}],["Give me a drama/romance movie in English directed by Greta Gerwig.",{"entities":[[10,23,"GENRE"],[33,40,"LANGUAGE"],[41,49,"WORK"],[53,65,"PERSON"]]}],["Show me the highest grossing movies that were released in France.",{"entities":[[58,64,"GPE"]]}],["Which comedy movie trilogy is Todd Phillips famous for?",{"entities":[[6,12,"GENRE"],[30,43,"PERSON"]]}],["List all the movies that Robert De Niro has starred in and are in the crime genre.",{"entities":[[25,39,"PERSON"],[44,51,"WORK"],[70,75,"GENRE"]]}],["Find all the movies that were released in Italy and are in the romantic comedy genre.",{"entities":[[42,47,"GPE"],[63,71,"GENRE"],[72,78,"GENRE"]]}],["Show me the top rated movies that have English and French audio.",{"entities":[[39,46,"LANGUAGE"],[51,57,"LANGUAGE"]]}],["Give me a legal drama series in English based on a law firm.",{"entities":[[16,21,"LANGUAGE"],[32,39,"LANGUAGE"]]}],["Give me a sci-fi movie about superheroes.",{"entities":[[10,16,"GENRE"]]}],["Name that Batman movie by Christopher Nolan that was shot in Chicago.",{"entities":[[10,16,"TITLE"],[26,43,"GENRE"],[61,68,"GPE"]]}],["Which Zack Snyder movie that got re-released in 2021?",{"entities":[[6,17,"PERSON"],[48,52,"DATE"]]}],["What's that 2022 Nicholas Cage movie with the long name?",{"entities":[[12,16,"DATE"],[17,30,"PERSON"]]}]]}